{
    "subject": "resource/Eryue_He",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/China",
    "human_readable": "Eryue He's nationality is China.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9224099516868591,
            "question": "Is Eryue He Chinese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.905994713306427,
            "question": "What is Eryue He's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7900146842002869,
            "question": "Does Eryue He identify as Chinese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.774682343006134,
            "question": "From which country is Eryue He?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7210789322853088,
            "question": "What country is Eryue He associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5622991323471069,
            "question": "Eryue He hails from which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5574691295623779,
            "question": "Where was Eryue He born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5383410453796387,
            "question": "To what nation does Eryue He belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47265228629112244,
            "question": "Where is Eryue He from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46809348464012146,
            "question": "What is the citizenship of Eryue He?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eryue He's nationality is China.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7758_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Eryue He from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7758_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what nation does Eryue He belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7758_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Eryue He born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7758_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7758_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information that confirms Eryue He, also known as Ling Jiefang, was a Chinese historical fiction writer. Therefore, the statement that his nationality is China is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}